別墅裡面唱K
bié shù lǐ miàn chàng K
Singing karaoke in my mansion
水池裡面銀龍魚
shuǐ chí lǐ miàn yín lóng yú
Silver arowana swimmin’ in da pond
我送阿叔茶具
wǒ sòng ā shū chá jù
Brought my uncle a Tea set
他研墨下筆直接給我四個字
tā yán mò xià bǐ zhí jiē gěi wǒ sì gè zì
He ground the ink and wrote words with one sleeve lift
大展鴻圖
dà zhǎn hóng tú
"Blueprint Supreme"
大師親手提筆字
dà shī qīn shǒu tí bǐ zì
The master grabbed the pen, laid them words down fresh
大展鴻圖
dà zhǎn hóng tú
"Blueprint Supreme"
搬來放在辦公室
bān lái fàng zài bàn gōng shì
Brought it to the office, now the office is blessed
大展鴻圖
dà zhǎn hóng tú
"Blueprint Supreme"
關公都點頭
guān gōng dōu diǎn tóu
Even Guan Gong nod his head
鴻運不能總是當頭因為
hóng yùn bù néng zǒng shì dāng tóu yīn wèi
Luck can't always be leading the game, 'cause
他說要玩就要玩得大
tā shuō yào wán jiù yào wán de dà
He said if you play, play it big
賊船越大老鼠才坐得下
zéi chuán yuè dà lǎo shǔ cái zuò de xià
Make the ship big, so the rats get in
得罪小人沒關係
dé zuì xiǎo rén méi guān xì
Offend a snitch? I ain’t losin’ no breath
得罪君子我看不起
dé zuì jūn zǐ wǒ kàn bù qǐ
You do right ones wrong? That’s some clown shit.
世上君子不貪杯
shì shàng jūn zǐ bù tān bēi
Real ones don’t be chasin’ the drink.
等於得罪了道
děng yú dé zuì le dào
Might as well disrespect the whole culture
黑灰藍白道亦有道
hēi huī lán bái dào yì yǒu dào
Everyone’s got rules that they call code
逆流才會水漲船高
nì liú cái huì shuǐ zhǎng chuán gāo
Go against the current if you want your ship to float
愛財如命的人沒有義
ài cái rú mìng de rén méi yǒu yì
If money is all you care, where’s your soul?
我說是對兄弟不是pusy
wǒ shuō shì duì xiōng dì bú shì pusy
I’m loyal to my brothers, no sucker role
細佬安之若命
xì lǎo ān zhī ruò mìng
Some stay calm, accept their fate
顛佬聽天由命
diān lǎo tīng tiān yóu mìng
Some go crazy, leave it to fate
攬佬拿把霜之哀傷
lǎn lǎo ná bǎ shuāng zhī āi shāng
I grip Frostmourne like a warrior king
劍指妖魔革命
jiàn zhǐ yāo mó gé mìng
Slicing through demons, revolutions I bring
人太沉迷收米
rén tài chén mí shōu mǐ
Too obsessed with cash, they'll miss the cost
人情軟過玻璃
rén qíng ruǎn guò bō lí
Feelings delicate like sugar-glass
江湖總是形形色色
jiāng hú zǒng shì xíng xíng sè sè
Streets are filled with many masks
誰還沒點詬病
shuí hái méi diǎn gòu bìng
Who doesn’t have a haunted past?
阿叔喜歡看風景
ā shū xǐ huān kàn fēng jǐng
Uncle just loves a mountain view
街頭中無道
jiē tóu zhōng wú dào
But in these streets, morals get chewed
攬佬要沒錢也得博命搵
lǎn lǎo yào méi qián yě děi bó mìng wèn
Even broke, a real one still fights through
勞力士還是AMG
láo lì shì hái shì AMG
Rolex or AMG — what’s true?
別墅裡面唱K
bié shù lǐ miàn chàng K
Singing karaoke in my mansion
水池裡面銀龍魚
shuǐ chí lǐ miàn yín lóng yú
Silver arowana swimmin’ in da pond
我送阿叔茶具
wǒ sòng ā shū chá jù
Brought my uncle a Tea set
他研墨下筆直接給我四個字
tā yán mò xià bǐ zhí jiē gěi wǒ sì gè zì
He ground the ink and wrote words with one sleeve lift
大展鴻圖
dà zhǎn hóng tú
"Blueprint Supreme"
大師親手提筆字
dà shī qīn shǒu tí bǐ zì
The master grabbed the pen, laid them words down fresh
大展鴻圖
dà zhǎn hóng tú
"Blueprint Supreme"
搬來放在辦公室
bān lái fàng zài bàn gōng shì
Brought it to the office, now the office is blessed
大展鴻圖
dà zhǎn hóng tú
"Blueprint Supreme"
關公都點頭
guān gōng dōu diǎn tóu
Even Guan Gong nod his head
鴻運不能總是當頭因為 (無錯)
hóng yùn bù néng zǒng shì dāng tóu yīn wèi ( wú cuò )
Luck can't always be leading the game, 'cause (No doubt)
騎樓混著，66 大順 man we good
qí lóu hùn zhe，66 dà shùn man we good
In the arcade shadows, we roll with flow — 66 smooth, man we good
(無錯)
( wú cuò )
(No doubt)
騎行越秀，小北淘金我的 hood
qí xíng yuè xiù， xiǎo běi táo jīn wǒ de hood
From North to South, the street hustlers chasing gold — that’s my hood
(無錯)
( wú cuò )
(No doubt)
帝女花，是我的 《California love》
dì nǚ huā， shì wǒ de 《California love》
The sorrowful love story of a fallen princess
聽任劍輝跟白雪仙，在白雲吃個農家樂
tīng rèn jiàn huī gēn bái xuě xiān， zài bái yún chī gè nóng jiā lè
Listening to legends on cassette — Cantonese opera, dim sum breakfast
太平館西餐廳搬了，但精氣神還在這
tài píng guǎn xī cān tīng bān le， dàn jīng qì shén hái zài zhè
Taiping Western Restaurant moved, but the soul stayed rooted
敵人幻想變泡沫，像燒臘店的外賣盒
dí rén huàn xiǎng biàn pào mò， xiàng shāo là diàn de wài mài hé
Enemies vanish like foam — takeout boxes from the BBQ joint
路上買個九爺雞，火鍋裡燙個娃娃菜
lù shàng mǎi gè jiǔ yé jī， huǒ guō lǐ tàng gè wá wá cài
Grab some roasted chicken, toss in baby bok choy
那宵夜來自大排檔，我們卻被人當大牌
nà xiāo yè lái zì dà pái dàng， wǒ men què bèi rén dāng dà pái
Late night eats at street stalls, but folks treat us like high-class boys
廣東人喺北京，唱住粵語 rap man we Stand up
guǎng dōng rén xí běi jīng， chàng zhù yuè yǔ rap man we Stand up
A Cantonese in Beijing — still spittin' bars in my native tongue
話 Stand 唔到概，d 佢到佢阿媽都唔認得
huà Stand wú dào gài，d qú dào qú ā mā dōu wú rèn de
If they try to stand in my way — I’ll break 'em till their mama won’t recognize 'em
喺珠江 skr，當我賽龍舟，然後啫啫煲，同 飲 涼茶
xí zhū jiāng skr， dāng wǒ sài lóng zhōu， rán hòu zhě zhě bāo， tóng yǐn liáng chá
On the Pearl River, I race dragon boats, then it’s clay pot rice and herbal tea
ughhh，cook cook cook
Uhh, cook cook cook
中華小當家
zhōng huá xiǎo dāng jiā
China’s ultimate kitchen boss
廣東街頭潮流trendsetter
guǎng dōng jiē tóu cháo liú trendsetter
Guangdong’s streetwear trendsetter
海印打口 CD 箱子肩背著
hǎi yìn dǎ kǒu CD xiāng zi jiān bēi zhe
Carrying bootleg CDs from Haiyin Market over my shoulder
在那 spa 游泳池，水質必須夠乾淨，這是"潛規則"
zài nà spa yóu yǒng chí， shuǐ zhì bì xū gòu qián jìng， zhè shì " qián guī zé "
Even the spa’s pool gotta sparkle clean — that’s an “unspoken rule”
老字號絕不會變味了
lǎo zì hào jué bù huì biàn wèi le
Time-honored brands never lose their groove
叉燒包加蜂蜜點綴著
chā shāo bāo jiā fēng mì diǎn zhuì zhe
Char siu buns glazed with honey — chef’s move
吃的粽子絕對是那鹼水的
chī de zòng zi jué duì shì nà jiǎn shuǐ de
Our sticky rice dumplings? Always alkaline-cool
大展鴻圖，我練字練累了
dà zhǎn hóng tú， wǒ liàn zì liàn lèi le
Practicing calligraphy with sweat on my brow
Then I pusssssh
Then I pusssssh — full power now
別墅裡面唱K
bié shù lǐ miàn chàng K
Singing karaoke in my mansion
水池裡面銀龍魚
shuǐ chí lǐ miàn yín lóng yú
Silver arowana swimmin’ in da pond
我送阿叔茶具
wǒ sòng ā shū chá jù
Brought my uncle a Tea set
他研墨下筆直接給我四個字
tā yán mò xià bǐ zhí jiē gěi wǒ sì gè zì
He ground the ink and wrote words with one sleeve lift
大展鴻圖
dà zhǎn hóng tú
"Blueprint Supreme"
大師親手提筆字
dà shī qīn shǒu tí bǐ zì
The master grabbed the pen, laid them words down fresh
大展鴻圖
dà zhǎn hóng tú
"Blueprint Supreme"
搬來放在辦公室
bān lái fàng zài bàn gōng shì
Brought it to the office, now the office is blessed
大展鴻圖
dà zhǎn hóng tú
"Blueprint Supreme"
關公都點頭
guān gōng dōu diǎn tóu
Even Guan Gong nod his head
鴻運不能總是當頭因為
hóng yùn bù néng zǒng shì dāng tóu yīn wèi
Good luck won’t always lead the way, because—